Inventory of the World Without War Council records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Printed matter (Box 522-532)
  - Political Observer (Coalition for a Democratic Majority), Special edition issue, undated; 1978, May (Box 527)
  - Population (Population Crisis Committee), 1976, July; 1977, January, September; 1978, June; 1979, April, 1981, June (Box 527)
  - Population (United Nations Fund for Population Activities), (18 issues), 1976, 1978-1984 (Box 527)
  - Population Crisis, 1970, September; 1972, July; 1973, July/August (Box 527)
  - Post War World Council, (8 issues), 1964-1967 (Box 6)
  - Prioritas, (8 issues), 1976-1979 (Box 527)
  - Pugwash Newsletter, 1969, July, October; 1970, January, April (Box 527)
  - Quaker Service, (15 issues), 1971-1974, 1976-1977, 1981-1982 (Box 527)
  - Quaker Service Bulletin, Fall 1973 (Box 527)
  - Radioactive Times, 1978, Spring, Summer, Undated issue (Box 527)
  - RAR (Reverse the Arms Race) Newsletter, 1983, January/February, March/April, November; 1984, January, May (Box 527)
  - Relay-Inform (American Friends Service Committee), (35 issues), 1973-1977 (Box 527)
  - Religion and Democracy, June 1982 (Box 528)
  - Resistance News, 1981, March 12; 1982, August, November; 1983, March, July; 1984, March (Box 528)
  - RF Illustrated (Rockefeller Foundation), (18 issues), 1972-1978, 1980-1983 (Box 528)
  - The Rights of Man, (12 issues), 1964-1966, 1968-1969, 1973-1976 (Box 528)
  - Salt, (14 issues), 1981-1983 (Box 528)
  - Sane (Northern California Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy), 1966, October; 1967, April (Box 529)
  - Sane Action, September 13, 1983 (Box 529)
  - Sane Outlook, 1971, August; 1972, March (Box 529)
  - Sane World Quarterly, December 1973 (Box 529)
  - Shalom (Jewish Peace Fellowship), (12 issues), 1972-1974, 1976-1980, 1983 (Box 529)
  - Shalom (Union of American Hebrew Congregations, Northern California), 1966, April (5 issues), June (2 issues) (Box 529)
  - Signs of Reconciliation, 1983, March, Autumn (Box 529)
  - Simple Living, (11 issues), 1975-1979 (Box 529)
  - Socialist Tribune, 1973, July/August, September/October (Box 529)
  - Society for Citizen Education in World Affairs, Inc., Newsletter, 1968, January, April, October; 1969, Vol. 7, No. 2, 1970, April (Box 529)
  - Sojourners, (9 issues), 1981-1982 (Box 529)
  - Soka Gakkai News, July 1984 (Box 529)
  - Soundings (Law of the Sea News and Comment), 1983, January, May, November (Box 529)
  - South (The Third World magazine), 1982, August-October, 1983, January (Box 529)
  - Star (American Friends Service Committee), 1979, Spring, Summer, Fall, Winter; 1980, Fall, Winter (Box 529)
  - Student Advisory Committee on International Affairs (University of Northern Colorado), March 1973 (Box 529)
  - Students for a Democratic Society Bulletin, November/December 1964 (Box 529)
  - Students for a Democratic Society Regional Newsletter, November 1965 (Box 529)
  - Sustenance, 1977, October, December; 1978, February, May (Box 529)
  - Taking Off, 1983, April, October (Box 529)
  - Thirsting for Justice, Winter 1983 (Box 529)
  - Transition, (19 issues), 1974-1977, 1979 (Box 529)
  - Treaty Council News, April 1983 (Box 529)
  - Twentieth Century Fund Newsletter, 1975, December; 1977, December; 1979, January, June, November (Box 529)
  - UN Reform, (7 issues), 1976-1980 (Box 530)
  - UNA (United Nations Association) News, 1983, January/February, July/August, November/December (Box 530)
  - UNESCO Association Newsletter, March 1983 (Box 530)
  - UNICEF Notes, Fall 1973 (Box 530)
  - Union of Vietnamese in the United States Newsletter, 1973, October/November, December; 1974, January/February, May (Box 530)
  - UNITAR News, (8 issues), 1971-1973, 1975-1978 (Box 530)
  - The Uprising, 1973, March 10, November (Box 530)
  - U.S. National Commission for UNESCO Memo, 1969, July, November, Special issue; 1970, April (Box 530)
  - US-China Arts Exchange Newsletter, Spring 1983 (Box 530)
  - The Veteran, 1981, November/December; 1982, April/May, November/December; 1983, February/March, June/July, Fall (Box 530)
  - Vietnam Report, 1974, November, December (Box 530)
  - Vista, (9 issues), 1965, 1967-1968 (Box 530)
  - The Voice, 1967, October, 1968, October/November (Box 531)
  - Washington Memo, 1983 ,January/February, May/June, July/August, September/October; 1984, March/April, May/June (Box 531)
  - Ways and Means of Teaching About World Order, 1971, Spring; 1973, June (Box 531)
  - The Wingspread Journal, 1981/1982, Winter; 1982, Spring; >1982/1983, Winter; 1983, Spring, Fall (Box 531)
  - Women of the Whole World, 1971, No. 2; 1972, No. 4; 1973, No. 2; 1974, No. l; 1976, No. 4, Supplement to No. 2/714 (Box 531)
  - Women's Strike for Peace, Vol. 2, No. 4 (Box 531)
  - Working Together to Enhance Caring and Responsibility, November 1983 (Box 531)
  - World Citizen News, (12 issues), 1978, 1980-1983 (Box 531)
  - World Education Reports, 1974, June; 1977, October (2 issues); 1978, September; 1979, January, May (Box 531)
  - World Federalist, 1982, March, June, September, December; 1983, March (Box 531)
  - World Federalist Association of Northern California Newsletter, October 1983 (Box 531)
  - World Federalist Letter, 1972, June/July, July, October/November; 1973, March/April, >May/June (Box 531)
  - World Federalist Newsletter, 1976, October; 1977, May, September (Box 531)
  - World Federalists USA, 1975, October 7, November 5 (2 issues), December 12 (Box 531)
  - World Goodwill Newsletter, January/February/March 1983 (Box 531)
  - World Hunger Actionletter, 1983, March/April, May/June, October; 1984, January/February, March/April (Box 531)
  - World Law Fund Progress Report, 1970, Fall, Winter; 1971, Fall; 1972, September, Winter (Box 531)
  - World Policy Forum, Spring 1983 (Box 531)
  - World Research INK, (17 issues), 1977-1979 (Box 531)
  - WPTF (World Peace Tax Fund) Newsletter, 1982, September; 1983, Summer, Winter (Box 531)
  - Miscellaneous brochures, pamphlets, leaflets, etc. (Box 531)
  - Miscellaneous brochures, pamphlets, leaflets, etc. (Box 532)